Phil McVay

Flat 2 Eden Vale, 13 Elizabeth Place St. Helier, Jersey JE2 3PN

07700 362073 phil.mcvay90@gmail.com

Profile

Highly self-motivated, organised, reliable and hard-working individual when presented with any task given. 6 years experience in customer service roles and 3 years experience within the finance industry. Comfortable working within a team or alone. I am sure, given the opportunity; I will be an asset to any employer.

Key Skills

- Organised
- · Pro-active
- Teamplayer
- · Quick learner
- · Excellent communication & people skills
- · Works well under pressure
- · Fully IT & Microsoft Office literate Excel, Word, Outlook

Experience

iPOP Digital - Web Developer (Jersey: St. Helier) - 2017-2018

- · Developing bespoke websites for a variety of clients.
- · Maintenance, adjustments and editions of existing websites.
- · Dealing with general client queries.
- Tools/Languages used: HTML, Jade (HTML templating language), CSS, SCSS, Javascript, jQuery, Twig (PHP templating language), Craft CMS, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Bitbucket (GIT version control system), Toast CSS grid framework.

Social Security - Operational Support Projects Officer (Jersey: St. Helier) - 2016-2017

- Managing various Health & Safety, Eco-Active and general business projects.
- · Reviewing and compiling up-to-date documents and procedures.
- · Assisting with general administrative duties.

Standard Bank - Custody Operations Officer (Jersey: St. Helier) – 2010-2012 / 2014-2015

- · Ensuring the timely settlement of Unit Trust and Market trades.
- · Processing client payments.
- · Processing of client FXs.
- · Reconciliation of daily cash activity.
- Writing/updating task procedures.
- Competent training ability.
- Maintaining the bank's Custody and Management fee database. (This included distribution of fee advices to clients, providing monthly accrual figures to the finance team and debiting/updating the client's portfolios.)

ODEON Cinema - Multi-Functional (London: Kensington) - 2013-2014

- · Floor duties (Cleaning of screens, screen checks, toilet checks, taking tickets,)
- Retail duties (Selling refreshments, cleaning off all equipment, temperature checks, up-selling to meet targets.)
- · Dealing with customer queries

Cineworld Cinema - Multi-Functional (Jersey: St. Helier) - 2009-2010

- · Floor duties (Cleaning of screens, screen checks, toilet checks, taking tickets,)
- Retail duties (Selling refreshments, cleaning off all equipment, temperature checks, up-selling to meet targets.)
- · Dealing with customer queries

Barratt's Shoe Shop - Sales Assistant (Jersey: St. Helier) - 2005-2009

- Organising & maintaining the stock room.
- · Floor duties (Serving customers, up-selling to meet targets, cleaning of floor)
- · Dealing with customer queries.

Education

• Le Rocquier School (Jersey): 2002-2005

· Hautlieu School (Jersey): 2005-2008

• BIMM London: 2012 - 2016

Qualifications

- Higher Education: Level 5 Diploma of Higher Education Popular Music Performance Level 3 BTEC Diploma - Popular Music Performance (Double Merit)
- AS Level: 2 AS Level passes (A* E)
- GCSE: 8 GCSE passes (A* C) inc. Maths & English
- Other: Digital Jersey Coding Programme 6 month course

References

Available upon request.